No, no. So Bita, you a dirty bitch, you know what I'm saying? I'm just saying, you a dirty
ass bitch, man. I'm just saying though. But let's see who in the chat, you know what I
mean? Shout out to the chat. Let me go to the top, man. Let me go to the top. It's been
a minute, you know what I mean? Since I've been live, you know what I mean? Well, I was
Come on swag. Why you come on swag. Come on swag. What come on swag come on, man
Yeah, I mean, I don't mind the word though, you know, be the love the word though, man
You know, I mean, it's alright. You know, I mean be the love the motherfucking word
I mean, hopefully y'all can hear me man. I won't know till I get to the bottom, you know
Shout out the cascade in the building
Yeah, I mean
built different in the building
Remember seeing your T board just admitted she talks she stalks you
I'll do I believe it man. They probably trying to report this motherfucking live right now, but
Hey, it is what it is motherfucking. I mean shout out the beep beep who got the keys to the Jeep
We don't know you know I'm saying we don't know but shout out the beat
Hopefully it ain't that bum bitch pez man. I got some shit beep. I don't know if you know about it beep
But you know pez was bragging, you know on how she got her her seed back
Yeah, I was saying and I found out how she got that seed now big T
She might be actually telling the truth on how she got her her seed back
You know, I mean, but the circumstances of how she got her seed back. It's gonna blow your motherfucking mind. You hear me?
I mean, it wasn't her being a good mom.
She's still a bum bitch ass mom, you hear me?
I'm just saying though, she a bum bitch.
But it's sad, you know what I mean?
It's sad, you know what I mean?
Yo, I'm kind of fucked up.
I might end this live, man.
I ain't mean to say resting, you know, P-I-S-S,
that's something I normally say to the juice,
you know what I mean?
But that was a slip up saying, man, you know what I mean?
I'm hurt.
You know what I mean?
That I even said that.
That was definitely accidental, nigga.
You know what I mean, I'm gonna have to send you some bread nigga. You know what I mean for my for my fuck up
I mean
Raging day man. What's going on? Bum-ba-glad. Yeah, I'm saying you you know, you're not Jamaican
But yeah, you know what I'm saying nigga. I mean shout out to you. I mean, what's the star for?
But shout out to you rager. Yeah, I'm saying fuck that bitch beat us rager, you know, yummy
She did you dirty man. She did me dirty man. I should have listened to you raging
I should have listened to you my guy. What oh my god. Oh my god
Who is that really crystal crystal come on? Don't clap me crystal
I'm gonna try to minimize your put your photos man. You're not the target. You know, I mean not today
Not today. I'm a not today beat up beta beta is
I raise your beat off
She
Come on, man. I be a petty man. Come on, man
Come on. Oh, holy lady be here. Get that bitch up out of here, man. Get that bitch
Chopped out of here. I can't see it cuz she blocked me. I don't want her in here chat classy
Yep, say all damn say I'm gonna have to all man. I mean
I don't want this person clapping people.
You know what I'm saying?
Damn, I'm gonna have to restructure my mileage.
You know what I mean?
Oh my God.
I should have looked at that earlier.
You know, they mad at me, you know what I mean?
I can't trust it, you know what I'm saying?
I can't trust you, baby.
I mean, let me redo this real quick, man.
Bam.
Look, as one, as one might get lost,
the other one get brought back.
You know what I mean?
You talking that shit, man.
Come on man, let me see.
Bam, you know what I mean?
Shout out to Trip.
Yeah, yeah, you over there talking shit.
I gotta look at the mama list.
You know what I mean?
I had beat her still mother.
You know what I'm saying?
I had to get her up the fuck up out of here.
I had to get psych up out of here.
You know, people was talking shit.
Hell no, you know, I'm good.
You know what I mean?
But you know, yeah, man.
Hopefully everybody having a good hump day, man.
I sure am, I'm doing good, you know what I mean?
I'm living my life, you know what I mean?
I got money, happiness, pussy, you know, I'm good, you know?
Hopefully y'all doing good, you know, because I sure am.
But let's get to this beta shit, you know what I'm saying?
We all know beta, you know, exposed Sandman family.
I already showed that, right?
I showed beta being a grimy ass.
Grandmom, you know, I'm thinking that's what she is. She's like 70 years old. You know, I mean she being grimy
Despicable, you know, I'm saying, you know, she doxed me on her platform for those that don't know on
about a week ago. You know what I'm saying? She docks me. You know, when I say she docks me,
she allowed somebody she don't even like, somebody that says she's on drugs, somebody that says
she's a bum, she's an old hag, you know, she's a drunk. Allow that nigga to come on Penel, right?
And change his photos.
Just to get at me, you know, for some reason she might have been mad
I didn't answer her phone call that day
She called me like twice and then left me a message like honestly to really think about that situation. She
Typically don't call me back-to-back like that, you know, I mean, so she probably was calling me to complain about somebody to be honest with you
I don't know who but um, yeah, man, that's me before you man
So anyway, she did call me that day. I was busy, you know, and then she went live
And, uh, yeah, man, you know, I went up there at first, Ron had a, uh, you know, his milk
dud, you know, profile, and he went and switched it.
You know what I'm saying?
But you didn't say the fucking thing, but all you handsome, that's you.
I said, oh, really?
You think that's me?
And y'all know how the story goes, man.
You know what I mean?
I spazzed at her.
She kept that photo up there talking about, she asked me and you said it was okay.
And, man, suck my dick, okay?
You know what I mean?
Stop my dick, Bita.
You know?
And yeah, you know what I mean?
That's how I go.
You know what I mean?
Bita, you know, betrayed me, betrayed my trust, and I said, fuck that bitch.
And I've been told her and everybody else.
You betrayed me.
Hey, Aldo.
Hello, man.
How are you coping with the situation here, man?
Oh, I can't get a day at a time, a day at a time, I mean, oh, it's like, I wish I was,
I wish I could say I was surprised.
Leave Vita the fuck alone. I mean, I don't know if you ever send any of those, but I mean, I'm sure I mean, it's like
I don't I don't I don't DM you say. Yeah
It's some text messages talking about I don't know if they can oh like from a number. Yeah from a phone number
I mean look from right now. I got several actually
At this point you might go leak that number because you know, they harassing you well, it's like, you know
It's just text now numbers. This one says
beat it better keep beat his name out your mouth boy you're done and i said you're going to jail in
response to them um let me see i mean it's like i might have four men on my phone and so and i'd be
allied i mean allies still around you know yeah i mean it could be i usually report these uh you
know report these messages like you know it's to spam or or like harassment or something and so
sometimes they just disappear but so i might not have a bunch of them on my um like save but yeah
these terrible messages.
They say they have many man since, you know,
putting a razor to his vagina.
There's, you know, so I can't really share them
on the whole thing on the screen sometimes.
But one says, this one says,
oh, here, when are you just gonna get over it?
You've made all the wrong choices.
You're too retarded to deal with the consequence
of the choices.
And it says, uh, well, that was, uh, it says, hello, read it to thing that is, um, eat shit, you fig, J.E.W. bass, bass, sort of quick, quick, um, yeah, that's like a bit of concrete stuff.
I mean, I think it was the ally because a lot of it was around that time of, uh, concrete and stuff, but yeah, I mean, I did.
Probably just report most of the messages so they don't have them, but yeah
That's only what I can see right now, but it has to be like up, you know hundreds of them
Yeah, yeah, it is well. Yeah, he does have a vagina
Who mini-manson?
But it is a it is a heat
Yeah
Pretty shocking stuff, but yeah, this is on rumble. I don't know was this lab taken down or not
I'm not sure what they try to do
No, not the second one that I deleted that one the first one was the they was trying to get me and I had to delete it
But this one I deleted or before
They was able to get it, you know, and then I get exposed today day. What is today day 4 day 5?
I think it's today's the final day day 5 man. Yeah, she was doxing J dog to you know looking for his information
So if people don't want to believe I can care less, my nigga, I'm still going to be good, you know what I'm saying?
Yes.
It don't matter, you know what I mean?
But she did, you know, send me his, his information and it was his wife information on there.
I believe it was his, his relative uncle or something like that.
That got some charges and, and then
And then J-Dog's, you know, information. So regardless if anybody posted it
She's transferring that information to who knows how many people what you think that people gonna do with that information
J-uh
J-Dog is her opp. She don't like J-Dog. You know I'm saying right J-Dog has admitted to sending shit to her crib
So like people want to play dumb, bro. What what is beta doing with people?
Information, you know Doc's information
You know be and then be to write a whole fucking essay on my post, you know me exposing her
Making up excuses. Oh somebody wrote that in my back chat cool
Somebody wrote that but you decided to screenshot save it and send it to people. Does that make you innocent?
What you out here fucking sending it to people,
knowing what some people are gonna do?
What you think sending it to me is gonna happen, Bita?
That I'ma just tuck that shit and not motherfucking,
you know what I'm saying?
Right because at this time I did have a my cash app was up and so it was just it would have been like
Oh, how do you send him the money? There wasn't a question of like how the money?
You know how to send me money really it was like, you know, and I look there's no I never received a zeal from
From elbow and so, you know, it's like he didn't say oh, you know
Oh, I'm gonna I don't know it's just like now. She's making things like oh
Well, it's about those for yours. You're begging for fish tacos that day or something like that or you know and
I mean, just ridiculous, she, and then, you know,
the different excuses, but there's never a,
and then person's coming up saying,
a person's gonna come up and say,
oh, well, I had that scrolling on my screen.
I didn't have my PayPal up on the screen,
and from the PayPal you can get, I guess, the full name.
And I've told my full name, you know,
that's not the biggest deal,
the deal is it was my phone number.
Um, yeah, so so what Christine is saying is that your name's been out there, right?
But be there sending your name your phone number and I still I got a look because I'm sure she sent me your address
My god, like I gotta find that shit. You know I'm saying like what's what's what y'all gonna say then when when I when I prove that
Beater done sent me that
Y'all gonna say that out for for zeal
And Bita had said, oh, look, she said, I give for you.
She said, look, I'm going to send you this stuff for your cat.
And it was a picture of a box with all this cat stuff in it.
And so I sent her my address, but she never sent me.
You gave her your address?
She never sent me the box for the cat stuff in it.
So she probably wanted you to give her that address
so she can probably hand it out.
I'm telling you, she didn't send you nothing.
Once you gave her the address, she didn't send you nothing?
Oh, no.
Never and so, you know
What's that about? I don't know. Where's where's the where's the stuff for the cats beta?
They said you had a ready to go in a box for them. I don't know never received that
So, you know, and she's gonna make you want to play captain save a hole or not be to a Christine
Talk about all his shit has already been out there Christine worry about your life bitch
You know I'm saying worry about what's going on with you cuz it I'm telling you you don't want to be next
I'm telling you just mind your fucking business Christine
And how they just target you and dot and dip and dodge me come at me bitch
You in beta come at me y'all dip and dodge and go at sight. I'm the reason this is happening bitch
You know I'm saying why are they going at you when I'm the reason they slithering around me to get to you cuz they
Yeah
Yeah, they think I'm just like defenseless and you know no one's gonna believe me anyway
But you know what I was kind of a punching bag. You know I'm saying you you you skinny you you you you gay
You know I'm saying yeah, you look a little weak
You gotta put you gotta you know I'm saying you gotta look like yo you ain't fucking with me. Yeah
Yeah, and orange be it's like because you know people think I am weak because like we got another person
Giving out all kinds of my family information and stuff and Christine and be the laughing about it never spoke out against it
Or they actually be the came in laughing about it actually we have a oh gosh. We have a big guess hold on
Oh my god. Oh my god. It's my you still not sleep. What's up slut? Come on man. Go to sleep. Yo, yo
Can you send me another picture of beta naked? I need a masturbate again. What up?
What up chat nah, because she's gonna privacy strike. So I'm good, man. I'm good
She gonna strike his chin or I can't you I'm I'm I'm I'm gonna let sight do a stuff
She needs a strike this day
You know, I'll send them to you and you you're still in same-man discord, right?
Yeah, send me send me the video. I'm trying to masturbate to it. I don't have no video be the
I know you got the video. Send me the video
See the hardcore porn video. I don't got no video. I
Don't got no video my guy
Yeah, I'm lying to me nigga. I could get the video niggie. No proper group shut your fat ass up man
Fuck you talking to like that. Niggie bitch. What the fuck do I think I'm up to fucking the ass
Needles, huh?
I'm gonna fuck you in the ass with needles
I wrote down my review. I'm all here some weird shit man. He's bizarre
Oh, my god, that was disgusting sick. I mean, say don't say that again. Don't say that again.
Yeah, listen, listen, slut. Holy moly. I'm gonna do shit to you that your homies would never
I mean, geez, um, yeah, just be sick just be sitting by his computer waiting for somebody to go live
Literally he in the same position. He in the same location. He just waiting on somebody
He watching videos and waiting on somebody to go live. Yeah, but yeah, I also played the clip of you know
I mean Alexander deleted this clip, but um, she was talking to Christine and she said
Well, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
you know because I have a clean record she said that nothing's gonna happen to me
you know i'll just gonna slap on the wrist and christine's like well they're just gonna see
his videos of what a stalker he is and no jury would convict you and so she's supporting you know
even physical violence and death threats towards me without without trying to de-escalate the
situation or anything she's she's she's escalating the situation uh so you know innocent little
Some of my shows on my Cult of Psyche channel, where I do play the one with Alex and Christine as the thumbnail,
and I do play that whole audio of that.
And so, I mean, there's proof. I mean, you can see what does Christine have to say about that? Nothing.
Nothing. She comes in here and tells me to leave Alexandra alone.
Me leave Alexandra alone. All I'm doing is responding to these criminal doxies that she's been doing almost every day.
My mother's my mother's picture my mother's name my family business all kinds of stuff, right? And so
No, uh
They won't speak out about that. It's just as bad as them doing themselves pretty much
I mean, I'm gonna say agree with that. So that'd be fine. Holy shit, bro. I got poochie sent me your address
Okay
Oh
shit
My fuck I just went and looked and found it. Yo
It does uh
Apartment F sound familiar?
That's my apartment, yeah.
Holy shit.
God damn.
Yeah.
So, yes.
Yo.
Look, it's been a bit of an impairment.
I just had a great, like, 12 hours of sleep.
And so, you know, I don't know.
Drugs, you know, I mean, drugs, you know.
I need to look through everything, my god.
Yeah, she sent me yo Addy, bro.
But it's not psychosis when I'm we're here with proof and receipts. I don't know yag are I mean it's like you're saying
It's the better means like hostess or something like that. Oh
This is what I'm saying. So does is psyche's address a part of zeal?
No, I got a thing your money. Do I got a putting your address? Nope. You just need my phone number for that. Yeah
Or I think maybe even email address or something like that and it was right after she sent
I don't know if she was spurging or she just started transforming
But this is around the time she sent me a J-dog shit too, right? She's a female stop being a baby
Okay, so females could just do anything they want the people that they just get away with everything, right?
I'll give me a bad name. Okay. Well, yeah, you do you do you get you I mean you you was fucking with Brandon and shit
Man, so yeah, but that's like, you know in the past, you know, I'm sure she means
I mean what I
What have you seen? Oh, we have your mark out here. Hold on a second. Holy shit
What's up, Princess?
What's up, King? How are you?
Doing good. You want to see my chest again site?
You've got it on speed down, I'm sure you've released to it several times. Yeah, you like that elder chest, don't you that elder chest?
If you saw below the chest you'd be amazed
Just like elderwood you got fucking both faggots. Oh, come on. Oh, man. Come on. We've got
No, go ahead. Go ahead. Call me out. Go ahead and prep press me bro. I
Just asked you leave my child alone. How about that?
Well, no, you both said about it cuz Karen did but you know, I'll digress
I'm sorry. No, no, that was the other day, dude. I'm not it. I'm a dude. I'm fucking high IQ. I'm not a fucking dumb-ass mother
You can use my picture all you want dude. I'll show you where I pee and poop you can do whatever you want with me
Leave my fucking kid alone, dude. I know I do leave the innocent alone. You're not innocent, dude
You can't you fucking ripped off the masian people for coffee. I'll fucking press them
We're fuckin' gonna have coffee.
Dude, that was the best content you've ever made.
The fuckin' Asian lady, fuckin' Asian lady
come out with the fuckin' old broom,
fuckin' beatin' the shit dude, that was funny.
See, that's organic.
You see how natural memes are made?
That's how you go viral, dude.
That's how you go viral when time is, you know,
what's up, Eldo?
I don't reform deldo. He leaves the kids alone, you know, he got a taste of the fucking nasty life
And now he's reformed a little bit now. He's uh, you know, he's tucking and rolling. That's what he does
He's got a donkey ass booty though. Have you ever seen a man? You ever seen that meme with that fucking dude with the uh
You know the fucking what are those shorts called Bermuda shorts or whatever that motherfucking donkey ass shit?
You got to watch what you do online because it's people like Nordcat that's gonna keep talking about somebody ass
Look that's better than talking about somebody's fucking kids
Diagrams let me die grants nigga
You want to see you want you want to see me in the porta potty again? I've posted a couple more for you
Oh, you got on in the porta potty talk about
Look look you you paid attention to that look I'll stutter a little bit
Anyhow without being said look look how you doing smelly hope you're doing good kiddo
Hope you're doing good. Look, I posted a few more hoping you were around to catch him so you can add him to the collage
You know like a kaleidoscope
Ghost of KZ is that fucking KZ dude? Take your fucking weird toothed ass up here and let's have a conversation
Oh, what it could go. He's got his incisors nigga. These motherfuckers talking shit about people's teeth with no incisors
Come on. That's enough, bro
you guys you know you're both in the codex i want to show you what the codex says about you guys
the codex need
it doesn't dox you doesn't dox you
i mean look at this point it's a fucking dumb what's up sig
I just want to see Sam and Sigg fucking Sam and pet and his little scuffed ass beard talking about I wish your beard was like
Eldos. Let's go ahead and go over here and get a little hot dog from one of the Brooklyn hot dog carts or wherever. Let's go to the
fish store. The only person that Sam had ever wanted to meet from New York, which there's a lot of motherfuckers. There's a handful of
Strong people from New York to San Man can hook up with and make content. He chose his sig sour
Alright, I'm gonna I'm gonna mute because I'm saying I gotta I gotta be I'm gonna mimic cement
What it says, this is NorCal I search for NorCal and this of the Oracle says NorCal
enters being bearing credentials the gauntlet the peer
institutionalized gay culture knowledge
which grabbed him before an historical standing.
He deploys his foundation strategically.
Cultural legitimacy becomes a scaffolding for escalation.
Five appearances cluster around confrontation,
open panels, and advice episodes.
His method is consistent.
Establish credibility, then shift register
from historical narrative into explicit sexual content,
then redirect the energy.
Damn.
Unconsenting.
Please, switch to sexual content.
That's never happened.
Well, that was the tiger butterfly stuff.
Yeah, that was did you know that serial killer that I'm look I'm gonna say it you remember that serial killer the one that
She looked identical to her and I used to type that in the chapter. She I can't remember her name
It was the ugly one the fucking one that's uglier than most you know, I don't remember her name
Well, what was her name chat?
No, no tiger butterfly looked exactly like this woman that was in a professional and prolific serial killer
I mean, yes, smelly.
Look at fucking smelly.
Come on.
No.
No, man.
Smelly.
What?
No, no, no.
Smelly.
I didn't say I asked a question with hold on a second. Hold on a minute. Hold on a minute. I gotta make a text
Yes, please hold on a minute
Gotta get them pipes situated. Go ahead man
Gotta get them pipes situated. Is is sick still backstage he cries
Give up, sir. Give up, man. Yeah
Oh, she looks like Eileen Warnows, you're saying.
Well, Eileen Warnows, the woman that killed all these men,
you know, she was, I guess, who played her in that movie
that South African actress, Charlize Deron, yeah.
She played Eileen Warnows in that movie.
Christina, pretty good movie.
Well, check it out, it's called Monster.
The movie's called Monster, guys.
It's based on a true story.
You need your insights wrote. So how do you get in the code? The codex is before the show. Oh, we have Sam man here
Let's hear what Sam has to say about this
Find your cat nigga. Find your cat you bitch ass nigga
Fuck sake in his fucking gay ass himself nigga
Nigga, look look he look he look look go ahead go ahead suck suck
Low job, Sam. Oh, yeah, look go suck his dick you bitch ass nigga
Three tricks nigga free the kitties
Get the lotion site get the lotion
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not gay. I'm gonna just eat
beat his ass.
Nigga, beat a doc's psych, nigga.
We outta here.
Nigga's psyched out to himself.
You know?
I'll give someone $100.00. If
they put where I put my phone
number on this. Yo, you used to
say your name in my chat.
Show me your phone number.
I got pulled up.
He just sent me his address.
He just sent my address.
Oh, look.
He's scared.
He was too scared.
What do you mean, nigga?
No.
He had no, uh, you know.
He just sent me that nigga
address, man.
Come on, man.
He does a whole lot.
He can't say she ain't sending
his ID.
Yeah, be careful. Be careful. She says anybody that she says she wants to send you a gift or something like that
She's probably just trying to get your address like she did to me because there's either
He didn't told me that she wanted me to she wanted to send me her dirty underwear, and I almost fell for it
Oh my god. Yeah, that's how she got your address. Oh my god. I almost fell for you. Well, that's shocking
I don't think she would send I don't think it would have been worth it
No, it probably made me throw up, you know, I don't know.
No, I mean, how long does the smell even last?
It just goes away, right?
No, they put it in a little sealed jar, you know.
She just take it off, put it in a sealed jar.
There's a woman that sold her, you know, her parts.
Yeah, I remember, I remember I was in this old guy's house
and his wife died like 30 years ago
and he was showing all his shit.
And he was looking through it and he showed me this little like do you remember the 35 millimeter film rolls?
Okay, what was on it? You know remember those he put um
He put like one of her panties. He rolled it up and he put it in the film canister
How much do you pay for that?
No, no, he showed me it. I mean, I didn't like I didn't go for like a whiff or anything. We've been weird
I she's been dead for 30 years. Oh, I don't think there was any smell
I'm not sure I mean, I don't know I'd be there wants to send me her dirty underwear. I'm down
Just don't give her your address. I'll just I'll I'll I'll join the stream and I'll have it
I'll be wearing her underwear on my face. I'll be wearing it as a mask
Okay
Wow and then and then when she sends me something it's gonna have a return address, right?
I'm gonna to her return address. I'm gonna send her there. You can get a mold
Did you know that you can get a custom molded dildo of your dick?
Can I get one of yours? I'm gonna I'm gonna send her a custom molded dildo of my dick
So she can fuck herself with my dick whenever she wants add one two
Bye
Well, you got to pay a little bit. Okay. I pay for it
Hi guys
What's up bros? No, what are you doing? What's up with that car? Whose car is that you're driving? Oh?
it's my um
I have a very, I have a very odd grandparent.
So one of your grandparent passed away.
They threw a wand, they threw their wand,
and they gave, they granted me the wish of a 2001 on the element.
Oh, you're like Mando.
You're like some Mando Indians.
You're like some Mando with a fucking element.
Hey, look, look, look, live your best life.
What happened to the e-scooter?
Sure, that's what I was thinking.
NorCal, the thing that I feel bad about people like you,
people like you, you have it so good,
but then you just got to open your mouth.
I feel bad for you.
Oh, the thing I feel like it doesn't help your is you look like you have a cleft
You probably
Shave that fucking weird-ass shit on your face
You look like a creature. I'll feel bad for you
Let me see what the fuck is that
Look, what's that attractive man take off my shirt and his luxury Manhattan
Dude, dude, I live in poverty in the squalor low key
I feel bad for you because I think narco
I think even if you had a hundred million dollar mansion, you would still be a miserable little shit
Thousand percent that's that's the sad thing. No, no, no people people have everything and then there's still miserable little shit
Yeah, dude, you remember why I wanted to like, you know, take you under my wing and be a bad father in terms of
I know you're an old man and you're doing well, but like
I'm not doing that. Well, there's no better fix this misery problem. Look, you can't ever get fixated never think you're something
You're not look. I'm a nasty fucking miserable man, and I'm trying to make myself happier every day
Now, whether it's me, you know, getting a little drink from down the street or whether
it's me taking 30 minute trip to get a, you know, a 10 milligram induced, you know, marijuana,
marijuana drink, you know, look, it's all the same.
We're all trying to escape reality, right?
Psycho-awakening tarot.
Yeah.
We are.
So that's why we have such good, good, fantasizing minds and the ability to.
I can tell by looking at you because I'm a former meth head not I'm not saying you are
Hear me out. No, no, dude. I used to fucking get high dude. I used to I grew up across the street from 1% bikers
I know everything about crank. Listen
You look good today. You look good. Listen for you. You look great today
Look, you look great
Now don't put your fingers near the camera because then we'll see where you've really been digging at
Listen, I don't know what you're doing, dude. You need to buy a carton of whatever you smoke and stop digging in the ashtray
Just
Pro tip pro tip stop digging stop being an ashtray minor that means a minor like people
You know, it's okay to grab a long one
But if you're gonna dig up and twist and like, you know smoke fucking nasty ass cigars in a pipe, you're fucking crushed
You're cooked
I'm a nicotine addict more than anything look I fucking dip zins fucking we're on the nines right now
They just came out with the nines you ever tried zins this little package. He's stuck in your feet
Yeah, yeah a little little like real cloth things. I've never seen you do them. I've done them before but it's like I really didn't care for
My I'm afraid of like, you know, like like a gum cancer or something from I'm not
No, what's up? So where did he go?
So did he just say that one of his grandparents passed,
and he inherited a Honda Passport?
Is that what I gathered?
Yes.
Congratulations, Sigg.
Why don't you drive yourself off a cliff you fucking weird beer freak? Oh
Man, come on. That's light work. That's nothing. That's like telling sick
I that's me me loving sick deep in this community. That's me wishing him the best come on
Eldo, you're gonna fucking get at me for that with all the things you've done
There's nasty come on smelly that was child's play
I was child's play that was me actually wishing cig is best life. What's up trip?
Or if I catch you like talking shit about me again another chat
Come on. Thank you called you mountain. He's still got a wrench all these times
Since fucking since fucking the Mesozoic times or some shit
No doxin dude fuck doxin that's weak
That's what weak people do because they don't have a vocabulary or any kind of fucking personality
Right, right, although
Damn
Yeah, you're right. You're right. Hey, look look dude. I don't give a fuck
I kind of like your fucking weird ass dude. I I mean, I can't it's not because it's not because the other motherfuckers like you
I'm just judging by our interactions, right?
Dude, you're a piece of shit, but who isn't at the end of the day, right?
Who you talking about?
I'm talking about you, Donkey Booty.
Oh, come on, man.
Man, what are you going to do?
Docs my kid?
Oh, no.
Come on, man.
That was a...
Who did that?
That was a chicken, I think.
Oh, shit.
Look at you with the big memory, dude.
See, you're the smartest brown man in the community.
I'll give you that.
Chicken.
That's not saying much, is it?
Sam, man, come back up here. Papa. Oh my god. Oh my god. He don't mind it. Kate. Oh my god.
Can't go get mad. Oh shit. Yeah. You better pay attention. If you let's leave Kate alone.
Let's not ever talk about kids. Yeah. Hey, Kate, Kate is up there in the fucking hierarchy.
As far as this community goes now. Look, that being said, hey, Kate, I hope you're having a good fucking summer.
But if I went up loser, I see you bro
Take the rent is back
This motherfuckers never gave me a wrench look, I'll never want one I want to earn my wrench the old fascia way by grinding
You motherfuckers are all fucked your mind blown is it is it Arthur is it Arthur?
I bet you taking more gay dick in your ass than this psych-awakened sterile guy
Exposure
I
This is B to working with Karen
Damn so be the tattoo so the BKG tattoo for old-time sake
Shit purple army
Yeah, I changed it. Oh, no, I know you changed it, bro. Is there the day you changed it?
Right read this now, where's when or all good warlock have a black cat Norris outside right now because
I heard him, huh? No, no, no, no. All right
Norris fine. She's like she's really good at it. Yeah, and black cats don't get fleas either. So you're good there big dog
Yeah, all digress. Let me look at Aaron provided. Oh, look at this. What Aaron Carter?
What do you know about Aaron Carter? Have you ever seen his sperm count?
Motherfucker could lay out a fucking load like no one ever. It looked like cottage cheese coming out of the end of the man's penis
I saw it. I'm a homosexual. Oh my god
Fucking molded hay from a professional source, but I'll digress
I'm glad you're over here loser. What's up, bro? CX purple army. Never forget
You know for banning people once the stream ends. Well, oh shit, dude
I mean you gotta stop timing people out and shit unless they're like Doc's and your family
But look at you go back to Alex mayors after all she's done to you
I cosign with what she's done. You're fucking twisted never forget Alex mayors hates me for a great reason, right?
She doesn't like me because
Because I fucking trolled the shit I ever made her go to Florida to meet a fucking dude that died his skin black
Oh, my God.
That's me, bro.
Nuka Zeus.
Ask her about it.
I shall tell you the same
Dude those DMs I still read them from time to time whenever I get bored
No, let me guess I've been drinking tonight. No, sir, I got off work just recently
I had a little twisted tea and I mean the
Teaching strong teas. I ordered a case of them. So what?
Okay, if I catch a buzz before my family gets on meldo, what do you think?
I'm saying no, do you have a family? I've heard rumors
There's nothing wrong with raising some fucking woman's kids and ain't yours, right?
No, no, look at me. I'm not dude. I'm talking about Zaya
That's crazy. Come on man, dude. Look if you don't find humor what I say, then you don't get the fucking joke, man
This isn't that serious these people act like this is everything to them like you psych
This is the internet bro. It's not that serious now you get you you start you start playing with fire and you get burnt
I don't want to hear about it. If you're gonna fucking sit there and grab coals out of the fucking barbecue and say
Oh, my fingers are numb now from birds
About you fucking with Alex dude after you got wrecked
You went back like a little poverty kid
Dude you're desperate for attention I get it you're on the internet we get it
I'm not fucking shitting on you
I'm just gonna bring it to you in a way you can understand.
Okay, you knew what you wanted to do, but leave my family out of it, y'know?
No, no, I agree, dude.
And if I was you, I'd take a trip to Texas and go ahead and fuckin' get you a fuckin' barbecue plate of dark snack.
I think I can, I think I can.
Go there and do what needs to be done.
She hasn't had her cheese plant in some time. I need you to enter her and give her the child she needs
Double vision
I'm going to the store get some
You need to go to the barber
Fucking the homeless man
Huh, what's going on with beta? What's going on beta? What happened with beta?
Sorry, you got my me too. You know I'm saying we keep it evening. I mean when you get back
What the fuck is that little gray black bush up there? What is he filming?
Psych pay attention to what you're doing bro. It matters
Now cam slips happen bro cam slips happen
but you've showed yourself in peculiar positions
and all sorts of stuff.
Hey, everyone, Alex mayors turned off the chat.
Ooh, we're so afraid, we're so scared,
we're so upset about you, Alex, not turning the chat off.
Oh, Alex, Alex, you need to find yourself a boyfriend,
a real one, not a virtual boyfriend,
somebody that actually loves you.
Find love, Alex, you need it.
Come on, man, this guy is fucking me.
Come on.
You good?
This fucking dumbass fucking psych.
Like, what are you doing, my nigga?
Huh, dude, that was the funniest shit this guy's ever done when he fucking went in there and tried to fucking like
Swindler like wheel and deal with these Asian people like like like there are those people
No, you know those are Croatians. You want to we you know wheel and deal and get a 50 cent cup
This motherfucker tried to fuck with Asians. Don't play that way, dude
Asians don't give a fuck. They will eat your cats
I didn't steal anything from the 8th of that stole.
Oh, that was funny though, dude. That was actually funny
Just like when you used to go up to the taco stand and try to you know, how about I give you five for four
You know, whatever the fuck you were saying, dude, there's nothing wrong here. These ain't swap meats, bro
That's what happens when you're dealing with swap meats and you know yard sales and shit. These are businesses, bro
You know shut up to you for you know, you know being white, you know, there's nothing wrong with that
Where are you going now dude? What are you doing?
You ain't got a lighter my man
What do you want to go grab some uh meet the dealer like what are you doing you want to go?
How loud that fucking that fucking clicking on that stove was
Oh, these got a lighter now. All right
Ooh, enjoy enjoy
But I quit smoking for some time now, but what store you go to site I go in markets
Your bands your band from all Asian
Wherever you live right now, I'll go right now
Go show an Asian
Once you take us to a bathhouse and get all these
He's closeted male homosexuals on these platforms excited.
Take us to a bath house.
Bath house? I want to go to one.
You've never been to one in your life.
I've never been to a bath house. No, I never have.
Have you ever been to a gay bar?
Um, yeah, I've been to gay bar.
I've been to gay bar.
Of course you have.
Just like J-Dog, you both faggots.
I got a straight.
I got a lap dance.
I got a lap dance in a, not by a gay guy, but by a woman in Mexico.
My brother's brought me a lap dance and it was like, oh, it's cool.
Do your brothers not know you're a gay man?
Yeah, I was probably like in my 20s. Oh, they were trying to convert you back to back to the pink. I got
She had nice boobs and she had like they don't kind of um was it the glitter on her boobs gay men hate boobs
They'd rather have a smooth chest with a nice nipple pay attention
But a gay man like nice boobs. I mean everybody likes a pair of like well, no
Well, you know fag hags do but real men like ass like giant ass cheeks
like something, you know, boobs are where milk comes out
for babies, I'm just saying.
That's part of the thing is like,
I mean, once you go down to the, no,
that's not part of the thing.
Part of the thing is the vagina and the asshole
and the ass cheeks and the breeding hips and all that.
Nipples are cool.
I like a nipple.
I mean, trust me.
Yeah
You know those nipples that are like to like grow I mean there's weird shapes nipples
You talking about them puffy nipples is that what you just said? Yeah, they got like the big they look like the fucking
The top of a bottle, you know, they
What about you all though, what are your favorite nipples?
I don't know what the fuck y'all talking about.
We're talking about nipples, nipples.
I'm not a nipple person, man.
What are you, an ass man?
Hello.
Come on in the locker room or I'll just like you know, we're in the steam room together talking about
If you've been with the elder if you've been with the woman that if you would play with her nipples whatever
You know like pinching, you know squeezing hard that it would completely get her aroused to the point where you'd go down there
And it'd be soaked like a fucking like a dish rag
No, I know the story but when I like I gave like a woman like I think I fingered her and that's like she like
I don't want to hear stories about a gay man doing anything to a woman. I'm sorry, bro. No offense
Well, no, no, I'm just kidding dude. That was a joke, man. I mean give me a sense of humor by now. Come on, dude
Everything I say on here is fucking for laughs. I mean, I'm not that serious
See you take it way too serious. You're getting all mad and screaming and yelling like look dude
You gotta lighten the fuck up dude. Lighten the fuck up. I'm trying dude. I mean, you know
You fell into the web of deceit from alex mayors dude. It happens many people have been where you are
Yeah, just ignore her. I'm trying to go away. No, you're not trying to you're not trying to you're literally doing the opposite
Well
Norca I want to be honest you asked me what am I am I'm not really a nipple person. I'm more so like an ass person like
I'll give you an example. You have say something like this. You have say
Me if you're gonna ask me a question I can't answer that's not my problem
I mean, don't give me started norca
Go, go, go ahead and throw out what you're going to throw out.
But that look someone said something about baloney.
Look, that looks like somebody took her ass and took it to a baloney slicer
and took the thick cuts like like they did in trailer park boys
when fucking bubbles and shit did that.
That bitch got a she's on.
She's she's she's she's she's she's doing a boomerang.
Ma fucking a stance, you know, what it looked like.
Her ass, the way she she's set up don't look like a boomerang.
I'm annoying Arthur really well a lot of people say it look
It's better than being you Arthur better than you bro. I'd rather be annoying to be you Arthur no offense
No offense and I'm a I'm a slight fan over here.
Oh, he know he know you to the attraction right now.
So he just want to trigger you so you can mention his name.
No, now I know who I know who are.
See, the more you can pay attention to the chat and like read without like
commenting on who you think alts are.
What's up, Arthur DeSoto.
Arthur DeSoto.
I mean, look, I don't try to call out all it's often.
I mean, look, Q45 with the fuck that guy, he's fat, he's ugly, and he's got no fucking
penis.
That guy's all bottom and no top.
Q45 is basically your closet homosexual.
Prove me wrong.
He's got more interest in men than women.
Tell me, tell me, tell me different.
I only talk shit about people that I think are lurking.
Q probably lurking, Q probably lurking.
Q, where are you at?
Come on, Arthur, dude, you're taking it too serious.
You're wowing me, bro.
You remember when you fucking talked about fucking suck and say is dick dude. That made me laugh
You got him so Twitter pated that uh, he exiled you from the sneaker sniffer community, you know
No more snipping for you Arthur. You're done. Is a closeted gay guy. That's definitely Arthur. I mean
Well, I mean I've said some homosexual shit, but I'll die. Not like Arthur
Why why you think he meant it?
What about that time I said I had more gay porn on my tablet than anybody in this community see you see what I mean I mean
Well, you got it. No, I said that I said that that was a statement
I make that Sam and like to replay over and over trying to like call me out for something
I said that you know Sam and
Get the fuck back. Did he did he come up here when I went to order some Mexican food?
Yeah, he did. Yeah, I love a person came up here to fucking
God, I would like to see where that that guy's teeth
Most of the weirdest teeth. How did you and him started like going back and forth though? Like did you see me salmon?
Yeah, or you just don't like no, I like stand man. That's the difference. See I like fucking with him because you know
I can say dang yeah, man. Why are you sucking my dick nor Cal? Why are you guys talking about men sucking your dicks?
That's the gayest thing I've ever heard right site, right?
I mean if you want to mend to suck your dick or talk about men sucking your dick
You might be a fucking actual queer. No kids
Come on you all fairness you got confirmation from a gay guy. Yeah, man. Yeah, come on man. That's right
That's what where else to get the deets on the fucking the real one the real gay shit, right?
No, there's no Arthur versus NorCal beef dude. See there's no I don't have a beef with anybody dude. I just don't I mean
You know
Stop going so low to where you have to fucking attack people's kids and I'm cool after that
I'm you can attack people for all they want and I'm saying this light-hearted Lee
I don't want to see you know people that docks. They just have nothing better to do like Alex talking about your mom and shit
That's fucking just gross dude. That's gross, you know, didn't she just have somebody pass away in her family
And she's gonna go at people's families and shit while you're still grieving over your dad
No, no, I quit it dude. It took me years to get over my my fucking parents back
Well, she said about me. She said well, too. She said well, my dad's big
She said her dad's been gone for over a year. Mine's been an offer two years
So that's that's enough time for me. It's not enough time
To everyone's different. There's no time, you know, there's no time
You can't the fuck is she to say how long it's gonna take to grieve over somebody dying
Imagine being her agent owning a fucking shitty ass car
Alex is a fucking loser, dude. She calls everyone else losers, right?
She's the actual loser hopping around from Airbnb to Airbnb because she fucking can't hold something down because she's a creature
I'll digress fuck her
Am I wrong? Am I wrong, Chad?
No, fuck her, fuck her.
No, no, no, I mean, what does she think?
She's the fucking moral authority of this fucking place.
Bitch, you're a leech and a creep.
You're lucky to be here from Bobby Dillon
fucking you dragging in here.
You know, shout out to Jess Chen for fucking changing her,
changing her digress tubes.
Fucking Willie gets it, dude.
No, no, who the fuck?
I mean, I'm nobody, dude.
I'm literally nobody.
I never professed or proclaimed to be anything.
Dude, I you'll never hear me say oh, I'm this or that cuz I ain't nothing dude
I ain't shit and I'll never claim to be but you got that alvex mirrors over there. Good evening. Hello wherever you are
Whatever bitch shut the fuck up
You're a fucking failed porn star dude seriously
Hey attention
Does your floor look like this like be honest, man, let me see is that my floor?
No, that's actually probably what you look like but now that your floor probably don't look that bad
No offense. That looks like you you fucking over at good times probably where you know that guy's gay, too. Yeah
Yeah, don't don't start demotating now
Told her that I was like pleasure myself backstage on a show
This thing's not bad, see?
Fuck, so let me ask you, Skid Row Camps 3,
did I slander Alex by the shit I said?
Look, that bitch just slandered more people
than she's created the word slander.
Fuck her, dude.
She ain't shit.
Right, she doesn't do that.
Now, as far as her grievance for, you know,
for her, you know, Ken passing away,
I can relate to that.
Because I've had a lot of people in my family die, but look you can smoke their packs snort their ashes
Fucking rise above for like a phoenix and fucking kill him again
I wouldn't bother me at all. You ain't gonna offend me by talking about the people in my that I loved fucking died
I don't give a fuck. That's gay. Imagine being offended by that. Let it go. Who gives a fuck?
This is the internet dude, seriously. What are you gonna do? You're gonna talk about my dead mom and if in me
I mean pay attention dude. That's gay shit fucking tired of that shit. Yeah
That shit dude fucking people so worried about that. They don't get this community and never will see there
You know, you get somebody saying oh, you know, you're this or you're that dude fine
Dude, if you can't find humor in your own fucking dismay and then you shouldn't be around here
This is not a place for everybody
Right.
This isn't the place for everyone, Psyche.
Now, see?
Now, you know, I know your mom's still around because Alex told me so.
Right.
You know, I know your dad passed away because you told me.
Right?
Right.
Now, with that being said, don't give her what she wants.
See, look at you making.
I, dude, I'm paying attention because that's the thing that,
and I'm sorry to laugh at your responses to these people attacking you.
Well
Like she's putting a picture of my parents and with lizard tails and green skin and using a picture of my deceased love one and show
I'm sorry. Look, so what you're fucking mom's probably a gecko. I mean, maybe she's maybe she's a skink
Gorgeous and she's not a gecko. No, I didn't say I didn't see I'm just talking
Man come on man who me
My mom's alive.
Is this like your mom passed away?
No.
My dad did.
Oh, you're dead.
At least the one who told us is dad passed away.
Mom's alive and she's putting my mom's name out every day.
The ghost of Casey, you fucking get it.
Everyone can get it.
And if you can't get yourself,
then you shouldn't be around here.
If you can't look in the mirror
and fucking desecrate yourself
and talk the most shit about yourself
without nobody helping you,
then you shouldn't be around here.
Hey, here's my abused cat.
This is my abused cat, Lola.
She's just like so uh i'm choking her right now of course. Oh, dude. Dude. I mean psych listen, bro
I seen you picking fleas off your cats. Don't don't don't don't don't act like it didn't happen
See, I go my cat. I go my cat. Hey, who's this jadeus grape cell at bono? Who's this?
I don't even let me see. Who is that? Come on, man. Come on. Get him out of here. Don't get porn bomb. Don't get porn bomb
No, it's bad. It's almost in the chat. Oh
Is that picture now looks like who's that picture?
Don't know
Charges on my nine
Fuck that game I don't fuck with them. He's a home. Oh, yeah, that's a crazy out. I ain't gonna lie
But they got my, my, my girl last name in that, you know what I'm saying?
Say, come on, man.
Dude, you can't honestly tell me that you'd fuck controller.
I want you to quit with all that nine shit.
That bitch is a three and a quarter at best.
It was talking about if you don't look at her.
God, damn, you got a weird scale, man, where you're at.
How you gonna tell me she don't look?
Come on, she don't look fuckable.
You telling me them titties,
them good old titties don't look fuckable.
Come on.
Hey, look, hey, look.
If she never spoke a word and she was freshly showered,
I mean, I'll give you that.
The second that fucking nasty mouth opens,
No, no, sir. That is the least sexy woman I've ever heard or seen on the internet. And I'm talking about I've seen some ugly, nasty creatures.
It's the way she talks, dude. It's weird, bro. She's, she's, she's, she's, you know what she's starting to look like to me? No offense to her.
But she's starting to look like a fucking drag queen, a nasty little drag queen.
Do you want to see that? It's pretty funny. Well, you know, it's like, because I am, am, um, yeah.
Willie, thousand percent, an actual real creature. That's the beauty of it.
Fucking weird motherfucker, dude sitting there pandering to fucking people on vertical
You know what she's you know, she got mad at me. Hey, I'm got mad at me because of um, she said I set her up
She looked good with the whole Brandon thing, but now she's like say brand is the smart
She's the one setting everyone up. Don't let her trick you sir
She's a bit smarter than your average bear. There's no two ways about it shit imagine her trying to make you
Oh, so what? You don't believe it or do you believe it?
And you fucking with that fucking creature that was your downfall
Well, that was a downfall after the downfall comes the rise, you know, i'm like a phoenix. Ah, well
You have to be determined, isn't it? Well, it's for two people in chat not doing too bad right now, you know
That's what it is. I mean, it's like, I'm not monetized, but it's like, you know, so I mean, I'm here to, like, have it.
Fuck you, loser. Fuck you, loser. I see.
Oh, for God's sake, you telling me that you wouldn't smash something that looked this good? Come on, brother.
Let me see what you're talking about.
Come on, man. And this was back when she was a little heavy set. Now she lost this weight.
Huh? Who is that?
What you mean it's my nine this back then you know what I'm saying but she don't fuck the way you know see now see now see look at me
You pull up something you pull up a little snack like that see if let me put them
Let me put my thumb over her face. Let me put my thumb over that face. Okay. I would smash that thousand percent
It's a real man to be able to fucking you to be able to ride that ride. I'm just telling you right now
A lot of you motherfuckers couldn't you ain't got enough meat to even crack that smile pay attention
Pay attention you little small dick niggas. You ain't got shit
You ain't I'm gonna look Alex has been making me laugh dude. Listen Alex is funny
I will not ever take any way from her humor and her fucking
Fucking with today. I was watching her video and shit fucking getting ready for work and taking a shower driving to work
and and during the first
Yeah, come on. We all talk shit about each other. That's what we do for fun. That's how we let each other know we we enjoy, right?
All the fuckers. No, anyway, she was like when she fucking goes and I will fuck that motherfucker
Which she does that shit, dude. I fucking bust out laughing wherever I'm at. I try to like hide because in her. What the fuck you laughing at?
What are you laughing at, right? Dude, he's fucking passionate about this.
You want to hear something? I mean, I can, I can, I can show you when she starts screaming,
screaming at me. It's like, it's sounding like the exercise. I mean, it's like one second.
You got a burning joint USA, a beat a mod in here is a mod? Like.
We're gonna join is Nick Johnson. That's Nick Johnson. He's my friend. No, isn't he a beat-a-mod to I don't care if they're beat-a-mod
It was a simple
A couple people. No, no, no. It's the way it is. I'm not trying to tell. I'm just I just a visual
I saw I'm not trying to make more of it than it is bro pay attention
Hey, he's trying to stir some shit up. I see. No, no, I'm not you dude. You're obvious with it
But it's you know, it's all right
It's him. Oh, yeah, you're beyond obvious
Captain fucking obvious at most shit listen listen, but they fall for it though
You know who's fall for it the idiots the idiots fall for anything
There ain't everybody here's you got to be you got to have a hundred IQ even fucking play around here
Yeah, if you don't have that I mean dude, that's that minimum just like music biz Marty
You got to have at least a hundred IQ to get his humor. I mean seriously, I don't know if you know who that is or ever spending any time
Come on, I know he was I know he was I know he was
Look, you gotta go way back farther back. I've been watching that I was watching that guy rest in peace music biz Marty
That motherfucker was funny, dude
He was funny in a way that it took you a few seconds to fucking content to gather what he was saying and then it was fucking something you'd never forget, like a joke you'd never forget.
He gone.
He ain't gone. He was the shit, bro.
Dan Samman Olson and discord talking about psych and cater friends again and shit
Sam Samman's funny dude, you can't take that away from that guy can be very funny
Come on that guy can be very funny and the thing is it when he's not trying to be funny like when he's like
Reacting to things naturally like the way he would in real life. That's when he's the funniest
Just like when fucking Barry the turtle sent you
Psych awakens tarot homosexual to go at him and like hand her to him and he was
He was fucking he was he was elated with the idea that some man would be attracted to him homosexual remember
I'm talking years ago. This was a while ago
The first time you ever
Talked and said I took a panel for Sam and and Sam ends site. Yeah, I do it was like they're like that
The one and showed you the ropes right he's the one who told you to go over there and do it, right?
They can examine everything in totality should this ever enter the legal realm
Because I'm clean as a whistle
But he's not he's an active drug addict an active extortionist blackmailer slanderer
bully
Overall criminal no one likes a bully someone who maliciously
Harasses and stalks women after they told them to leave him
They told him to leave them alone. I mean, it's ridiculous
Who's the bigger girl?
This is why I attracted to big women like that. I fucking you an opportunity
To remove the videos doxing my family before this goes any further. I didn't set you up
You yourself
Injected yourself into the situation with Brandon then brought me into it further by staging his redemption tour
We all make mistakes. You know in your heart that you're going too far. I know
I mean, I continue this, but when it's like,
we have Sam in here, hold on a second.
It's funny, why worry about me?
Now I press Psyche by a fucking hang with fucking
Brandy Q and Karen, but niggas, they worrying about me.
I still don't got it.
Nigga, he denounced them stupid ass.
Go live
On panel you got a catabuser on panel why not
a cat abuser nigga nigga
Why do you want men to suck your dick faggot
To do his last thing before he might dropped was suck my dick
Man on a panel of men that guy is a gay
Yeah, yeah, we know look see he doesn't get it. I've already I've been pressing psych. You got to go into intervals
You got to do it. You got to do it slowly or cycle get triggered and spurred out
I didn't you're crazy
And your family were doxxed years ago. I see you like that. I'm sure
So how do you think I feel? Have empathy and end the cycle. And then he posed, and I can't believe the nerve of this part, he posed the Christian Bible verse, whereas he actively, publicly aligns himself with historically demonic entities.
Hold on one second. Here we go. Sam, I'm back.
There's like Kate hanging on your panel elbow right after she said you went after her nephew
Oh nigga, that was a recap. You stupid
Man anybody that does some demonic shit are all fucked up anybody
On sight panel right now, huh?
Case modded over here now
Boycott hold on
Boycott was strong
Oh
Boycott by the way
Anybody
There are two shaming people
Talk about all the people are missing feet Matthew seven mother fucker. That's your problem. You have no self-awareness, bro
You would have them do to you your ego Sam in the law before I drive up their killer for you
Bible verse advice himself, but let me re-read this
No one cares about this
No, even after the days that I am no longer breathing.
That's my favorite part that I have put out in regards to that's why I like Alex
Bates will remain online
Do it again make sure everybody knows come on, bro
That was I didn't set you up you yourself
Inject it yourself into the situation with Brandon then brought me into it further by staging his redemption tour. No
That is
No, you motherfucker. I'd all never forget Sam. I should suck Alex's clit
You could try to suck on her cloud when there is a mother fucker around a woman who truth be told is
Yeah, no vegan patriot
the only no
that
I even thought that they're psych you reacted to all these people now and change and want
it to be better to give him a chance and the moment that whatever now she's friends
to say the same shit yo so what you think I have to be cool with this nigga to be on the
panel oh my god I'm like I don't have to be on the panel nigga you're on the panel right now
I don't have to be cool with him though I can hear a cooker yeah a kettle abuser
Get to a music cat. Tell me what the flow? Oh, you don't use cats. Who me? No, I'm talking about
Abusing cats. Oh, you what are you talking about? Oh, no, I'm glad you're defending that
Good looking. No, no, I'm not just
Oh
I
So who are you? You're the moral police officer?
You want shit?
Why don't you get enough shit to a rib in your mouth before you fuck shit?
You ain't got two things in your mouth, what the fuck up?
Norkow, Norkow, he defends Alex.
He, Alex, he's the sucker for it.
He was an out-killer.
He was the key simp.
And he don't give you guys no self-awareness.
Yo, that's crazy.
Like, shit your skinny ass down, bro.
Yo, that was dope.
That was dope.
It's crazy, didn't even talk.
Man, shit about that.
And I said, yo, why you over there by ETC?
And they say it's a theft channel.
Yeah.
I'm like, yeah, but you can't even keep the same.
Hey, you don't say nothing.
Hold on a minute.
What is the second shot in a group opponent, dude?
Yeah, you didn't have nothing
Hold on, dude. You'll kill for me, DC.
You don't got it for me, bro. You ain't smart enough.
You ain't smart enough, dude. You ain't smart enough.
Sorry. Try again. Try again, Sam.
You ain't smart enough.
No, you're a loser, dude.
Type in the chat you think I'm part of it. I don't know
You're big ops
I stand on all of you, I can stand on my teeth, can you?
I stand on what you do, bro, when you stand on.
Boycott, by the way, enjoy.
Boycott what?
Now look at you up here, you dumb motherfucker.
You're an idiot dude. You can't cook shit. Go cook go cook Frank's and beans you stupid motherfucker
You ain't cooking shit Papa. He fucks the vibe up man. Norca
Getting spurgin out. Oh, he he says. Oh, I see you and day is set. That's like him have squeaky to it's a little
He's like a little chihuahua going
He's a chihuahua. He's a chihuahua. He's an old chihuahua is what he is.
He don't let nobody speak.
So
He saw me in pebs chat, so he's pressing me. Oh, no, you know your ETC
Why do you keep leaving it coming back you gotta gain your fucking composure in your breath
You want to drink it?
Elbow come from NTC, too, nigga?
Listen, you ain't talking about that to me,
he ain't talking about that to you.
Are you still watching, nigga?
Are you still watching?
Listen, I got here, listen, here, I got here.
What's up?
Come here.
Are you still watching?
That's the problem, you're still watching, nigga.
Is that the problem?
Or is the problem you fucking giving peps money
after you talked to your family?
Shut your fucking dumb ass up.
That's
Psyche
You got Peter telling you
You're a fucking puppet pop-up
Eldo, I want to I want to apologize to you man. I I know what be to get to you to and
What's that squeaky song that's you chewing on a fucking chew toy because you're a fucking animal
No, J-Dog, exactly!
J-Dog, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Although I'm sorry for what happened to you two.
I know both you and Psyche got hit at the same time for the same bullshit.
Psyche, how are you doing, man?
I remember when Mr. Cakes made you show up.
Oh, Mr. Cakes.
I remember when I made you show up.
I'm sorry, although I'm sorry.
I took my L.
I held my L.
I own my house. Yeah, he got me that day.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Come on. Yeah, he made you shut the fuck up nigga. Yeah, I make you shut the fuck up
Fuck up
Go learn about how the Japanese grow their teeth back
Fuck elbow. Yeah, nigga.
You took the thru-
No, no, no, no, no, no, fuck elbow.
Why do you want to fuck elbow?
Fuck ribs, bitch, you want to fuck elbows.
You can't even chew meat, bitch.
Fuck off.
I wonder why.
Do meat and then come at me.
Why you don't worry about your bitch that much, nigga?
What?
What do I worry about?
What, my family?
You can talk about my kid?
I came out for your girl.
You wouldn't know nobody wants to see that
Cam up for your sister
Demin you ain't shit
I'll fucking kick your ass bro, I'll knock your teeth out of the cell
You know I know the Lord nigga
You know my Lord, okay
With my Lord, he's not dating me bro, with my Lord
You're working nigga
I'm a ski angel
Yeah nigga
Ski angel, right?
Yes ski angel
Everything you know from your brother pussy, you ain't shit
Yeah exactly, yeah
You ain't shit bro, you're fucking pure
Yeah, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you talking about the girl playing at the time, you
What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do doctor my kid, bro?
You gotta be on the alcohol this they can think I'm hate think I'm an elbow
Yeah, I just said you called you you called your girl a fat bitch a hundred percent. I never said that
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I fucking drive up through the brook and clean your car.
Don't let your bro clean your car, papa.
Don't let a hoolie cook that for you.
Name by the way.
I don't want to give a hoolie cook that for you.
I don't want to hear it, man.
I don't want to know, by the way.
How you doing?
You know a shoe, though.
It ain't true.
Nick, go on everything I love.
I ain't lying, Nick.
Go on everything I love.
Hey, play it, man.
And you don't get into it.
I didn't mention it.
Damn, I'm out of here, man.
You're a fucking liar, man.
You're gonna go eat a real big piece of shit.
I'm a liar, but you're the liar.
You like them big, you just like them big.
Fucking beat his shit, you ass bitch.
First, it's Bill got you fucking ruined.
You're done, papa.
You're a liar, nigga.
No, you're a liar.
You're a liar. Yeah, I want to hear it. Somebody fucking bring this clip.
We call my wife a fat bitch.
Come on, my nigga.
Hey, no. Play the clip of me calling my wife a fat bitch there, man.
I just want to remember that.
Did you remember that?
There's plenty of people remember that.
Hey, play the clip of me fucking asking for panties, too, while you're at it.
Yeah, just like the music right when Mr. Kicks just a fucking squeaky mic.
You're a loser, Sam, man. You're a fucking loser.
So speakers bitch
You get a map is I'm trolling you with
A lot of things you like about being under that Persian spell
I ain't lying about that nigga. I ain't never lie. I would never put that on nobody
You know you said that I don't know why you won't walk in that. I never said that
To play the clip of me
I'll beat you out. I'll beat your ass over life. You know it's crazy
Maybe big tea can take you to your dentist
Yeah, don't worry, no cal, I'll talk to you later.
What's your name, NYC?
Fucking name your man, name yourself Clint, man.
You're a loser, bro.
You ain't shit.
I'm a loser, bro.
Kill your ego, Sam, man.
Kill your fucking ego.
Got a big ego. I'm not lying on you. What are you lying about me me saying I'm my wife's a fat bitch
Oh
You know is crazy you admitted to it. Yeah, I should drink back in the day
What some camp the content? Okay? Don't be a clumsy bro. Don't even mention don't even fucking mention fucking broke the little punk
I'll fucking knock the rest of the teeth out of your mouth. I never mentioned him
You would never know other people you have no fucking idea talking about
Talking about shit. You don't know
Right
And I know this man, because you're fat, because you're a fat bitch, I think that's true, man.
No, no, no, no, that's crazy, man.
Oh, that's hate, man, that's hate.
You're a fat bitch.
That's the shut up, man.
Hey, Samman, you're a fat bitch.
No, I told you I could pull your car.
You can't pull my car.
You can't pull nothing.
That's the Julio.
Hey, who the fuck in Julio don't have shit?
Kel J for the jump up here.
That's Samman in class.
Couple of the year
Stuck your fucking juice with mouth
Well fair
You enjoy site you're the one who wants men to suck your dick you're the one who wants men to suck your dick you enjoy site
He's a fucking faggot
Oh Sam, man, I'm gonna fucking fuck your dick so quick, Syke.
NorCalW.
Hell yeah.
No, fuck that.
There ain't no W.
I want, I want to see the clip where I said that about my fucking wife.
Fucking liar.
You know you didn't.
No, dude, I don't need him.
I know you don't.
He's triggering nothing.
That guy tries way too hard.
Sam, man, the fucking try hard.
He's a fucking tryhard. He's a leech and he's a preach.
Motherfucker couldn't eat a fucking rack of ribs if it's like dependent on it.
Motherfucker's fucking on chili dogs outside to taste greens.
Motherfucker's got Diane's back. Got a motherfucking science stick between his knees.
Motherfucking shit. I said hey, Diane, got a fucking run off to the city.
I always want me to suck his dick. I'll digress
It's like he how you feeling now after all you know, I know you had a you guys you and although I should be
For more, you know, I didn't use game for you guys feel more like, you know better about that
Like at least Vita has been exposed for being the rap bitch that she is
Yeah, I mean we all knew it. It's just units needed proof and now the proof is there and now, you know, everybody can see it
Yep, yep, do you feel it's like you do you feel are you honestly disappointed by it?
Like because if you look at the date
April 23rd 25 you guys were still good at that time like really good
right but and also you know what she said the reason was before there was no reason for this
dollar or whatever but she didn't she also showed that she'd docked my address to me like he found
what she said my address a month later so she said your address your phone number your full name
your bank account number your routing number your bank that you bank with dude that's like
six things already she gots you on so site was that your phone number or your bank number
Well, that's a phone number, but it's attached to the cell.
And so I don't know what else is on the platform.
That's a phone number.
Dude, all they need is a phone number.
You know a hacker, all they need is a phone number.
And all they need to know is your bank,
and they can get into your bank.
Like that.
So in a way, Bita kind of docks your account information.
She docks your money.
Well, I mean, I might have been.
He's on the money.
But yeah, I mean, it's like, she did ask, she said, she had a thing of catch-aways that
sent me in stuff, and I gave her my address, and then I never went to catch-away with her.
So, she put me a picture of this, like, I have this weird cat, see, and, you know, she never
sent it, so I don't know if that's part of her scam, is to, like, give her the address,
but then she's sending a nice gift or something like that, because we won't give their address,
so sometimes I'm glad they trust the person, which I did, you know, so.
Yeah, you had no reason. And then, Elda, what was the reason? I mean, if you don't mind explaining,
Elda, why did she send that to you? What was the reason behind it at that time? Why did she,
was she planning to dock Psyche the entire time or was it for leverage or...?
What was it about that we had a call prior to that message and I could show it was 28 minutes
Peter were on and off around that time, bro
Like they would go back and forth and argue like I don't understand what people don't understand her
Her psyche were like going back and forth
Yeah, and and honestly, you know when it comes to that number and address
Beat is the type to not to say something without saying it, you know, or I'm a get on we go
You know, I mean like shit like that. So she goes. Yeah, she's neat. This is a lot. She'll sneak this
So you don't you don't gotta say it and I know already what she you know, what she in 10
You know, or what she wants somebody to do, you know
Who backstage
I
Think that might be what's his name fucking um Brandon announced. I knew it was Brandon. I knew
You that guy dude that guy need to go crawl back under the rock he came out of like for real
Like he could just go back to his gaming shit and go chill over there. He
He ain't got no business here
I can't pull up will be the lives of the orange and I think she was like an hour away probably
She doesn't like to drive on a freeway either because afraid of the freeway or something
So she just drives to like you know her little 80s night that she goes to and that's it and then they know
Whatever else she does. She also has like us and kind of like festival. She's gonna be selling stuff out. Yeah
If you didn't know, I denounced Brandon and a band ran up on the show, and I'm not kidding, that's all I can do.
Whether it's for me or not, for that, you know, that's up to you, but it's like, you know, I did my part for money.
Dude, it's like, it's like, how come people don't know how to forgive?
Like, people want to hold grudges, like, for the longest fucking time ever, and not let bygones be bygones.
Everybody has gun shit to everybody, sex shit, put up pictures, you know, whatever it may be.
But, you know, the bigger man is the one who can forgive.
and forget and apologize and then move on and try to make amends like kind of like what you guys are doing
like
I never talked to brandon personally either people are saying. Oh, yeah, I never talked to one like on one-on-one or anything
He was always on the show and so I never had a private conversation with him about anything
Yeah, I mean he
Alex
And now she's giving him advice
You know
by a lot of people and you know so she didn't that's why she has three seats and I think it's fine to
say voicemail and stuff like that rather than being played by other people. Well she's just covering
her tracks well her back she's watching her back you know it's kind of like
When you go to Walmart, you're not going to throw the receipt on the floor. You're going to hold it
so that way the checker can see it, you know, so that way they don't accuse you of stealing later.
So that way, same thing with INX, if they try to accuse her of some lying bullshit,
you know, she gots proof.
I guess she was bullied by these people and weaponized by them. And so she decided to start
keeping receipts about it. So people will say, oh, well, you know, that was hard to prove it, but you
when it is on voicemails and stuff like that,
you can hear exactly what really happened.
So, first, do you feel better?
Do you feel better now, psyche,
that all this is that come to light now,
that everybody's like starting to, you know,
believe and see what you were saying
the entire time about Vita?
That's right. I mean, I don't lie.
No, I never heard somebody lie.
I know I know but I get called a liar I could call it and I call all these other things out of my like
You know slander of things like animals. These are like sandmackers up in screams about like
He unalived his dog with lean and that fool was high on lean, you know blicks out of his mind geeked out
You know he's passed out like this had the lean on the floor with the little fucking cup with the jolly ranchers and shit up in there
And then he fucking spilled it and the dog drank it thinking it was something else, you know
He did it Sam and on a live is dog. Yeah, but you can't
I well of my cats, you know
uh one of my cats thinks silly with black and white cat beautiful cat uh oh so what about what
about beata pulling her cat whiskers man nobody yeah yeah she plucked all of the whiskers out of
her cat's face like one by one but i'm just saying like come on man yeah i yeah that happened
But her thing was she accidentally hits the cat in the face,
all the kind of stuff, and it's like,
I never went after her by any of that.
So she goes after me and says that I killed my cat, basically.
Oh, my poor cat.
She calls it, they say it's a little bit of dungeon.
And they're out, and they're indoor outer cats.
Her cats are locked inside the house.
Not mine.
I don't understand why she's called it a dungeon.
They're allowed to go out.
I just want to have them have a cat door,
so they can come in and out and say, please.
You know?
Do that's like saying you're gonna keep a dog indoors and not let him go to the dog park like you let your you your cats are inside outside cats
You know, they they go to the rescue outside. They wander they do what they want mate
Then they come back inside and they come home and they eat and they go to sleep. I mean
All my guys I have right now are fake they're all fake you know they're I think they're two of them are fade one is muted
And so I don't know everything they say is a lie. There's a lie
Oh
Poor cat man. You see how half of the faces got misquiskers missing? Look at look at half of the face
Look on the left side of the cat the cat's left side look at they're missing they're missing
No, no the left side look at the left says she pulled them out
It's the lighting. It's the lighting.
See how there's none on that side right there?
Not the side where she's pointing the other side.
I don't see nothing there.
I want you to see.
You're so cute to me.
You see they're gone
Every one of your fucking little cutie whispers
She said it she's
Hard to watch that's very hard to watch
Wow
And then too, you can't help it what happens to the cats once they get outside like
You can't help it if they run into you know other wild animals while they're on there
You know their journeys outside like what's gonna happen is gonna happen and that's nature. You know shit happens
You can't you know
Keep them inside cooped up and the cats will never see
My cats are all like the boy cat. He was it was an indoor after cat his whole life. He's 17 or 18 years old
He hardly ever goes outside their cats Lenore and
Well, when Nora's a rescue and so is the most Bola and they were there used to be outside
I have been your cat so give me Jimmy like you know what my decision to let them inside or outdoor and like
huge amount of the population you're gonna say hundreds of millions of people are bad because
they let their cat indoor outdoor you're saying that's cat abuse i don't understand that it's like
it's cat abuse keeping them trapped inside of a house that's like a big cage like a kennel
their whole life like why would you want to keep an animal that originally was
Yeah, in nature they're born outside usually, you know.
Yeah, yeah, they're wild animals, they're feral animals,
like they're not supposed to, we domesticated them.
People, humans get it, not.
They weren't born that way that's what they're saying you didn't say it but they're saying but they're saying and they're saying that they're saying
Oh, he's like I because they got you by coyotes and what's they didn't they say didn't probably a
There's a not even a shelter this city. There's people take the cats in
I've seen some of my cats in neighbors houses like we don't have air tag callers and stuff like that
And so I think people will take them in it's like starting in like
around the streets and stuff like that, you know, it's like people love cats.
Yeah, yeah, but yeah, I'm happy to, I just want to reveal the truth and it's like, that's what I
really want. I just wanted the truth out and it's like, you know, a lot of people are lying, lying,
lying and saying really bad things about me and talking about slanderers, you know, it's like,
and then they're saying, I'm slandering. I'm not, I'm not, I've had the truth, they slander me, they lie.
Do those people probably feel stupid as fucking they were talking shit about you the whole time and oh beat of this
Beat of that and the whole time. She was the one doing the slimy shit behind your back like
But Nancy she has a whole whisper collection Nancy. So if it's hard to pull you know saying
Then she's she's probably cut down. I'm just saying
So I keep would you allow that like if you met her
And you see went over to her place and you seen her saying you know
Look at my whisker collection of the kitties and then she's you know plucking them in front of you
What would you do? What would your immediate?
I have a cat door. The cats go in and out as they please. I mean, it's a cat flap on my on the
bottom of my stairs. They go in and out as they please. There's also a backyard, large backyard.
There's large property they mostly stay on. There's also trees, inclinements, stuff like that.
And so I don't know what happened. Like why the coyotes got that one cat, you know, it's like
They shouldn't be it's not like it's I live in a normal city
But there is like an animal reserve and they don't be able to control the pickup coyotes and stuff like that
But I've never seen one, but it's like, you know, it was just a rare thing
There's a pack of them came out and they and they unfortunately got one of my cat
That was before he was and was on the show
So I can you drop the link
They shouldn't be walking around alone either.
Well, chibi chibi, you know, cats are not dogs.
Dogs shouldn't be walking around alone.
Cats usually can be indoor, outdoor.
Like a lot of people let their cats come in and out, okay?
We can agree to disagree, but, you know,
I don't live in like the middle of the woods
where there's just tons of animals around.
It's like it's a residential area, you know?
And the cats are all fine, you know.
You're like one guy hit by a car once okay, you can just agree
But you know what so you just agree with hundreds of millions of people that allow their cats indoor out
Okay, hundreds of millions of people. Dude. I've had indoor outdoor touch my whole life and they will always been cool
Dude, you fucking lied about how you've showed us the fake ankle ankle monitor shut the fuck up. Now listen Psyche
Fuck a piece of cardboard around your ankle shut your fucking mouth
That looks like you stupid motherfucker.
You're the one who's straightened a piece of cardboard
behind you so you can go live and show your face.
Look, hey, Psyche, you're the one who told us
you had a fucking family of wild possums
living under your couch at one time.
Died breast.
You ain't got no animal sanctuary outside of your house.
It's killing fields at best.
No
They were playing together so you had like
I had I had the cat had five
kittens and the kittens were
small. No one's saying you're
fucking you're sacrificing and
crucifying kittens on the tree
behind your house, dude. That's
not what we're saying. Yeah.
But we were the guy that was picking fleas on live stream
We need flea killer bro animal collars
We say he hasn't lost any cats in a while
The main poor there someone said that psych and the cats are just squatting there
I mean, that was the funniest comment I've read all week.
They were squatting in like a beautiful ocean side apartment.
And they were squatting in a movie for years.
No, bro, you're not getting it.
Dude, you're not getting it, Samman.
So you do you want me? I just pressed him. What do you want?
You tell me you tell me how you want me to act for you. I'll be your puppet pop-up
Let me tell you what I will do. I'll get a fucking steak medium rare chew that motherfucker to oblivion
I'll chew it into grits. I'll chew gristle
Attendance that man. What about you?
It's like you. What are you drinking?
What do you say? I ain't drinking. I'm not drinking dude. I had a fucking marijuana drink
Hell yeah, that's what's up
NorCal, you're looking guilty, NorCal, we weren't talking about you, NorCal, calm down.
Say man, he's always talking about me just like I am and what's up, Jen.
There's too many coyote ugly. Coyote ugly, Jen.
Oh, I thought it was a real brew. I was like damn psyche slam that beer quit
No, I didn't read that I guess all the bru
The fucking thing that ever happened was this guy was in the Asian ladies fucking chased him off the fucking broom. God, that was funny, dude.
Dude, I fucking, I started to, I started to, I was going to revitalize you.
What is up with, what is up with Alex?
And, oh, I'm sorry. Michael, say her name or no?
No, you used to suck her, used to suck her clip, bro.
You wanted that fucking Elmer's glue in your mouth.
Weird oh by the way
Don't make me care I'm up for you
You're done. I showed you my Peter low my chew to buy my teacher own no, no
Watch the
Yeah, so
Are praising that they're trying to say psyche was stealing when that wasn't the case
He tried to barter with the wrong people's what happened he got wrecked
Lucky didn't get that broom showed up his ass like clumsy in prison
If you're lurking clumsy
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Now it's time
Okay, bad you look worse in good times there, bro
Nice neighborhood you asked her you could jewer down for a fucking dollar. I asked her. It was a huge
I mean they run out like I'm robbing a store.
Go back in there and watch what happens.
I told her, I said, I think I, can you do a dollar on here?
That one.
It's okay.
Yeah.
Look at that camera right there, up there.
See it, everyone?
You're in a fucking crap door up there.
Okay.
Well, come on.
What are you?
What'd you do?
You tried to do fucking Asus, which you did.
I asked her.
Yeah, I did I ask you yeah, I asked her lady. Hey ma'am. She's a panna Graham ring by the way
They're offended like by your ring. It's like J dogs
You're cooked bro got wrecked
You raise your voice at me
She told me that it was okay.
Yes, she did.
Do you want me to play it back?
Yeah, play it back.
Wow.
Sike.
So look, remember Nancy.
Nancy.
What was it?
Me?
Pause it real quick.
Okay.
I'll be back.
So listen.
Listen, remember I said that Bita, you know, it was already rumors that she'd be pulling
her cat's whiskers and, you know, she said that she collects them.
Well, I got a video of the bag of whiskers.
you know, where she showed them and shit that she really collects her cat's whiskers.
And Nancy, you just said that that's just part of the flow now.
I'm just saying.
That actually happened.
See, you see, beat is funnier than you guys eat, you're getting dated by Dina.
You know what I mean?
Of course, his spell hits different, right, Odo?
You were under it big time
Hours you spent on the phone talking to be to behind the scenes
That's more time than you speak to your fucking let's talk about what are you talking about?
What does she talks about she used to talk about salmon she used to her boyfriend
Yeah, she's the shit on salmon
Oh, now he opened her kissing her ass now talked about thing, you know I'm saying
She talked about motherfucking
Talking about a lot, bro
It's word of mouth, bro, I didn't record her fuck our conversation here. I'm blocked you girl master. I see you in the chat
The clip hopefully
No, no, that's not how she made that fucking person's spell that you're under.
You and Sam, man.
Fucking simps.
Your nasty fucking
Yeah
I'm in big ass titties of hers. That's the only thing to stab booted all this cat whiskers
Nobody want to fuck with her like after that's just a one-man. Thank you, man
Nobody wanted like like be with her like sad man
She won't
That was like two or three years ago!
You fucking crazy! You painted a piece of cardboard around your ankle, you dumb motherfucker!
Nigga, that shit was like three years ago!
Um
Do you like I said you have resolve that means you're resilient that means you're like the fucking like you're like a creature
You're like a lizard you fucking shed your skin to come right back. You have no fucking remorse
You're resilient nigga said it out of her mind making threats
Yeah
Don't make me drive to Texas bitch
Roll Nate that far from
That's a lot more states and six you fucking
Florida go all the way you really are retarded
Geographer Tennessee and the rest attention nigga just go through Virginia and go through Florida
No, you have you have my bad. I'm fucking I'm fucking toad army. I'm ski mask mafia, bitch
I will do what needs to be done
Fucking shout out Joe shit, please fucking redhead and creach
Ass all the time when she gets out of her car looking around like Tommy said
Um, and it's ridiculous. So I'm doing this for a friend though, too
Because he just threatened his life news like and so they need to recording. So here we go
Someone not choosing to seek employment or things like that now he's able-bodied
Okay
I'll drive the fucking Rollies Nancy all this that really you go to the fucking when it comes to
parents and
If that's an equation then I was drinking fucking maybe it needs to be me on day
Considering things that he's doing
really because
They're not going to likely be able to lease certain properties on that property
Specifically because of him he has live stream. Am I starting my worst ideas, dude?
I had one little fucking twisted marijuana team
I ain't drunk man who probably has to wake up in the morning
Go to work, pay their rent, and they have to hear him at night, acting a fool.
That's the worst thing I ever did.
You're not fucking, you're not going to smoke anywhere.
I would say Tenon, I wouldn't move out, and I would choose the owner.
Well, there's the likelihood that that could happen.
And then on top of that, he's going to go to one of his local establishments.
and terrorize them, thinking that he can get free things, even if they're little things.
Why not be able to pay for them? Why not be, what about I think about
Because he lied to me a lot. I know a lot of people are like, oh, how can you be so gullible?
Well, excuse me for having a heart. Okay? Oh, okay. You sound like good
He lied to me a lot. I don't want the funds or any of that back. I want him to leave me alone
But because I donate to him extensively, he thinks he can keep coming at me.
He pressured me into a lot of things.
Keep in mind, I lost my dad, my best freaking friend in the world.
March 9th, 2025.
He knew that.
I didn't even know he was studying me.
years before that.
That has come to mind.
Have you ever asked for money?
This is an emergency.
Yes, yes.
What's the reason, RG?
I don't voice record people.
I don't do that.
But yes, he has.
No, that's fucked up.
He pressured me into a lot.
He told me things were an emergency.
What did you do to her to make her do that?
He made me feel bad about things.
Epa, what did you do to her to make you doctor family and all that? What did you actually do?
I didn't nothing. I didn't nothing. I asked her what I did for a minute. Ponder my question.
Here's what I did. She, she blames me for Brandon and Hugh situation. You can watch those.
Yeah, she plans to be she said I set her up to like look stupid with Brandon Q. Okay, and that's all
What you did she said you know what you did gaslighting right? That's what she said
My weakness says
Hey psych one second
Do you remember when you met her in real life and you washed your hair for the first time in two weeks and it was all frizzy?
I laughed my fucking ass off shout out ip2 remember. Do you remember that dude? That was good person
Keep doing that. Keep doing that
No offense. No offense. Love you
Love you
Not say that I'm a pretty strong resilient person. Okay. I am
but he
Use and abuse me and I'm sick and tired of certain people in these communities acting like I'm oh so big and bad
Cuz I'm not I went through something extraordinarily hard for me. Beater just went live site and for him
The panel restreamer let's go ahead
All those right this is an emergency life Christine take the panel and talk about fucking J dogs nasty looking skull cap
Skull cap nigga. There's no skull cap. Yeah, you know, it's it tapered like a fucking alien pay attention
No, it's just shiny. No, I'm talking about where it comes to a point like a fucking data gray pay attention
That's an angle you're looking at an angle just like in your mouth
Yeah, yeah, I like the geeking your mouth nor Cal you know what that is a angle. No, no, I don't but you do gay bar, man
Clubs ain't slinger. No, I've never been to swingers because I've been to a ton of gay bars
I love a big arm like that. I ain't gonna hold you. I love a big one
I hate it when she fucks with you, reality man. So you were cool with beta
See I was there reality Nancy she got drunk and got all weird on you that time, you know because you know you scrutinized her
You scrutinized beta. Hey, listen, is anybody in this community scrutinized beta more than I have?
I don't know serious question dude. I don't fucking scrutinize the fuck out of beta
Right, I mean, and I don't want no kudos. I'm just saying dude
Call it down the fucking middle for all of these motherfuckers. Especially this little faggot tripping sip fucking fucking
Testicle gargle and little nigga. Why do you want to hit on trip like that?
It's banter bro, I'm talking shit
And then Black Archie, and it's Gage,
and they're already pursuing me already, okay?
We all talk shit, psych, I just said you fucking...
What are they doing?
Are they in her chat room now?
You're in your backyard, who gives a fuck?
It's not true, dude.
They're talking shit right now?
Yeah.
Fine, it brings her down.
That's right, bro.
I'll fucking do a swan dive, nigga.
I'll fucking, I don't know what I'm doing.
Black Archie doesn't strike the shit out of that.
I don't fucking know what I'm doing.
Oh, yeah
You had a cover over it you had a cover over yeah, so nothing to strike you on
Are you out there are you sacrificing animals in your backyard on that tree you talked about
Then shut the fuck up and shut the fuck up bag it
Okay, I'm gonna meet
I go sub KZ. What's up this stage? Oh
Psyche you're not all everybody else in the world can restream me but you you're restreaming me
I got to get on my computer
Let me let me show the proof
You gotta end it and like delete it
I'm gonna go copy the link. I told them he is not allowed to restore me.
Hi.
I'll be right back.
There's no room for dreaming. There's a cover over it. There's nothing to restrict or to reward.
Hi. Hey, bro. Let me show, let me show the...
Hey, where is it at? Fuck.
I love her little tattletail people though. I love her little tattletails.
Who was it? Were they the ones over there saying that Psyche's restreaming you?
Yeah, Psyche. Yeah, this stage, yeah.
Oh, dang.
You can't have the chat right now. It says, uh, let's see, um, let's see, uh, evil.
She mad. She mad, bruh. Fuck her. Fuck her.
That's just one of the truths now.
What is this shit? This shit is annoying you, bruh.
Sike you should turn
DVR on so that way she can't rewind the stream and go back to and try to match it if you turn your
Yeah, turn your DVR on there ain't nothing. She can't match it the time stamp
Although you're gonna show some proof
I'm trying to
That's gonna be funny. Yes. Oh, you ready? Yeah, psych. Share this like share this cream real quick psych sure this cream
Sure this green this is beta. This is beta. This is why I said she plucked her with her cats whiskers
You got a whole whisker collection chat
Come on live stream advertisement
Lola not flashing the oh god you guys I'm telling you can you uh show us your whisker collection?
Are you gonna make fun of me again?
No
Okay, you probably won't
Bita did not pluck her cats whiskers
She just collects them when they fall off
I found one yesterday and I was afraid to tell everybody because not everybody but you in particular. I was like, oh, he's gonna say she just for fun.
This is crazy. I don't know how you can see it, but let's see. It's a lot.
It's on top of it's a block like look at that. Oh my god
You are not lying although you fucking proof right there look at that I swear
You know the Michael sheds up more shit's like I'm telling you thingy is that right now
I'm scared guys
There's some black ones in there. Yeah, there's a couple of black ones
They look at her worse. They're very bouncy
But I swear to him pluck them before the I've known I've known them. I've had these
Brush out of them. She plucked them. She says
There's some black ones in there. Yeah, there's a couple of black ones. They're very bouncy
But I swear they plucked them before I've known them.
I've had these kind of-
You should make like a paintbrush out of them.
I'm gonna make a book and then in the front. I'm gonna glue all the whiskers
That is that is some sick shit right there
Like where you go? Why are you running off site? I didn't mess in with this thing. So do you beat or don't strike him?
Oh, he's turning his DVR on or off so that way she can't time sample
Yeah
Well, she had people over there ratting and saying, you know, it's like he was re-streaming and
And he's like J-Dog is just such a dumb dog with a little brain he's just sitting over there like oh, yeah
But if I was to like really wanted to like dog J-Dog
Wouldn't fucking give some information that was back there J-Doc did a report on me like a appeal because he was using my ex's pictures
He was like threatening me so I did a report on him. He did an appeal and he put in his information all of that
Eldo by putting it out there not even like lining or scratching it out his name his information
But he's sitting there. Whatever blah blah blah
Who gives a shit?
I never docked so I can I put me in a list. I docked
I was letting him know that they're using his second picture is fucked up like why are you supporting?
Why do you want me to have to you and clumpy these people up when these people have them as they're fucking like channel pictures?
This guy goes for a far reach, but keep trying
What does you gotta do anything this bitches
She tripping she throwing everybody in the same
I remember specifically on your panel, but see you didn't dox because you're at least not like you're not a dumb fuck like people say you're like slow or whatever you
What do you call it? You scratched out his information and you were showing his harassing charges to somebody else
I don't even know that other female where he was harassing another female and he had like a court charge or whatever, but you
Blurred out or you you know
Took out his like name and information. It was already out there. Everybody had seen it
But you blurred it out. Eldo actually put it there on his community page. Mm-hmm. That's what Eldo is doing now
They have nowhere else to go, Luther.
They just been looking for an excuse
to go back to a pedophile supporter.
That's what they do.
It's strange.
Even if you hate me.
Whatever it is, you still don't go sit next to somebody who's supported Brandon Q who is known to be a doctor
I have like so many fucking like screenshots of
You gonna catch those please you're gonna catch them please you are hey Tom
PD, what's up? What's up key diamond? Hey Moshe, you want to say hi Mickey?
You're going to confront her.
You do?
Moonwalk.
It's the same.
Oh, and Elda is sitting over there saying that I pluck every single one of my cat's whiskers.
Are you fucking nuts?
And J-dog, I mean, J-dog said it, and then J-dog is like, yeah, and they grew out.
What the fuck is wrong with these people?
Show the collection.
What's new, baby?
Keep trying, keep trying, keep trying.
Hold on.
Hey, God.
Yeah, she watches.
God damn, she lurked it.
RG harassed my family, aww.
He did?
Damn.
What's up groovy eddies?
Groovy eddies?
I know Jane Shremp, but I know Alex created a whole war.
What?
Crystal, that's you and not an alt of you.
You're always just looking for war anyway.
That's what you do.
Now you threatened a dog to J-Dog now, you have my people's address, yeah, I had to put in my people's address.
I would never dox it.
You did an appeal, no I didn't, that was in the
back chat and everybody put your charge of harassing charges on Santa like it was already out there
but when you get your email you tell me your phone number you tell me your address
Okay, whatever, but yet you dox me you send me fucking. I don't know a frog rad whatever the fuck it was
I didn't send you any rats. You said you had participation in it. I have what I have a screenshot
It says
I just took credit for it
Then you did it then you're gonna take the credit. Why are you sending fucking female chef?
Know look at the top of that. It was a backstage somebody else had your information
You're a fucking harasser fucking J-dog
I'll tell you this there's a big W in your address. I wouldn't dox it. All right, just shut up
If I wanted to talk to you, I would have done it.
Now you're just a while.
Fuck.
What I'm saying?
Why would I want to do when I say that's not even your address?
That's not even your address would be the would be the would have chat.
You're like you lying.
Yo, what the fuck is wrong with him?
He's sitting here saying, oh, I got some I got some the fuck I didn't.
I wanted to dox you. I would have given LL your actual information where you fucking like appealed and wrote a fucking letter
What's up? It's me. It's like he's gonna restream you. I'm just gonna pure out at least